[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Do you think it's a game-changing moment in this election battle?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "game-changing", "moment", "in", "this", "election", "battle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "It's certainly an insight into the mind of Mitt Romney.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "certainly", "an", "insight", "into", "the", "mind", "of", "Mitt", "Romney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "Clearly, judging by the way the polls are moving, and the general mood about Mitt Romney, he's in trouble now, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["Clearly", ",", "judging", "by", "the", "way", "the", "polls", "are", "moving", ",", "and", "the", "general", "mood", "about", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "he", "'s", "in", "trouble", "now", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Well, certainly he's talking himself into trouble.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "certainly", "he", "'s", "talking", "himself", "into", "trouble", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "What do you think about his hand on the foreign policy tiller?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "about", "his", "hand", "on", "the", "foreign", "policy", "tiller", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Well, he's certainly been bumbling when it comes to domestic policy and way beyond his element and comfort level when it comes to foreign policy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "certainly", "been", "bumbling", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "domestic", "policy", "and", "way", "beyond", "his", "element", "and", "comfort", "level", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "foreign", "policy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Donald, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Donald", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Hello, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Hello", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Are the media making too much of this, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "the", "media", "making", "too", "much", "of", "this", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "One of the problems, it seems to me, is if you actually analyze the 47 percent who supposedly don't pay tax in the way that he put it, many of them reside in states that are supportive to Mitt Romney, so it's a real shoot-yourself-in-the-foot moment, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["One", "of", "the", "problems", ",", "it", "seems", "to", "me", ",", "is", "if", "you", "actually", "analyze", "the", "47", "percent", "who", "supposedly", "do", "n't", "pay", "tax", "in", "the", "way", "that", "he", "put", "it", ",", "many", "of", "them", "reside", "in", "states", "that", "are", "supportive", "to", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "so", "it", "'s", "a", "real", "shoot-yourself-in-the-foot", "moment", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "PERCENT": ["47 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Do you want to see him go harder at Barack Obama?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "see", "him", "go", "harder", "at", "Barack", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Well, I have to think that it's been, you know, a pretty rough period because everything he says, they attack him and I think he's going to have to get very tough and frankly, he's got to fight fire with fire.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "to", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "been", ",", "you", "know", ",", "a", "pretty", "rough", "period", "because", "everything", "he", "says", ",", "they", "attack", "him", "and", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "have", "to", "get", "very", "tough", "and", "frankly", ",", "he", "'s", "got", "to", "fight", "fire", "with", "fire", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 129, "question": "How can he work on that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "he", "work", "on", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 131, "question": "How can he improve the way that he relates to people?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "he", "improve", "the", "way", "that", "he", "relates", "to", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "RUMP: You know, as you know better than anyone, and I just want to congratulate you because I'm just hearing great things about your show and how well you're doing and I'm very proud of you, because of your success on the \"Apprentice.\"", "answer_tokens": ["RUMP", ":", "You", "know", ",", "as", "you", "know", "better", "than", "anyone", ",", "and", "I", "just", "want", "to", "congratulate", "you", "because", "I", "'m", "just", "hearing", "great", "things", "about", "your", "show", "and", "how", "well", "you", "'re", "doing", "and", "I", "'m", "very", "proud", "of", "you", ",", "because", "of", "your", "success", "on", "the", "``", "Apprentice", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Have you spoken to him since this whole secret video story blew up?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "spoken", "to", "him", "since", "this", "whole", "secret", "video", "story", "blew", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "I have.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "And how was he?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "was", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "I think he's fine.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "fine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Do you still believe fundamentally that Mitt Romney can win this election, Donald?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "believe", "fundamentally", "that", "Mitt", "Romney", "can", "win", "this", "election", ",", "Donald", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "RUMP: Well, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["RUMP", ":", "Well", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Donald"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Do you think that it's fair that super PACs can spend tens of millions of dollars and therefore, the one with the most money can, if they're smart, effectively buy an election?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "fair", "that", "super", "PACs", "can", "spend", "tens", "of", "millions", "of", "dollars", "and", "therefore", ",", "the", "one", "with", "the", "most", "money", "can", ",", "if", "they", "'re", "smart", ",", "effectively", "buy", "an", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", ",", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "NN", "MD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Well, number one, I don't think you can buy the election.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "number", "one", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "you", "can", "buy", "the", "election", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["tens of millions of dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "From your conversation with Mitt Romney, he's a bit battered but not beaten?", "question_tokens": ["From", "your", "conversation", "with", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "he", "'s", "a", "bit", "battered", "but", "not", "beaten", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Oh, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "How do you get him out of this hole?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "get", "him", "out", "of", "this", "hole", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Well, you know, there are only a couple of responses in a case like this, because it's hard to disagree with that analysis of this quote.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "there", "are", "only", "a", "couple", "of", "responses", "in", "a", "case", "like", "this", ",", "because", "it", "'s", "hard", "to", "disagree", "with", "that", "analysis", "of", "this", "quote", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", ":", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "What's he going to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "he", "going", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Well, I kind of agree with the idea that you do have to say go closer to an apology if not -- if not outright apologize.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "kind", "of", "agree", "with", "the", "idea", "that", "you", "do", "have", "to", "say", "go", "closer", "to", "an", "apology", "if", "not", "--", "if", "not", "outright", "apologize", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Isn't it a problem -- Michael Gerson, isn't the real problem for Mitt Romney is that this lends succor now to the argument that he basically is pretty two-faced when it comes to principles and his political views?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "a", "problem", "--", "Michael", "Gerson", ",", "is", "n't", "the", "real", "problem", "for", "Mitt", "Romney", "is", "that", "this", "lends", "succor", "now", "to", "the", "argument", "that", "he", "basically", "is", "pretty", "two-faced", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "principles", "and", "his", "political", "views", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Well, I think that the worst kind of gaffes are the ones that confirm a stereotype.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "the", "worst", "kind", "of", "gaffes", "are", "the", "ones", "that", "confirm", "a", "stereotype", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Gerson", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Do you think as things stand, that Mitt Romney can still win this election?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "as", "things", "stand", ",", "that", "Mitt", "Romney", "can", "still", "win", "this", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Oh, I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "What do you say to them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Well, Piers, I just go back to a central theme of encouraging everybody to vote, to search their own heart, because it's interesting, good people of faith can read the scripture and interpret it differently.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "just", "go", "back", "to", "a", "central", "theme", "of", "encouraging", "everybody", "to", "vote", ",", "to", "search", "their", "own", "heart", ",", "because", "it", "'s", "interesting", ",", "good", "people", "of", "faith", "can", "read", "the", "scripture", "and", "interpret", "it", "differently", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Who is more charismatic to you?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "more", "charismatic", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "I think they're both amazing men.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "'re", "both", "amazing", "men", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Are you undecided?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "undecided", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 368, "question": "You have decided?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "decided", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Well, I'm going to really enjoy watching the debates because I think --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "really", "enjoy", "watching", "the", "debates", "because", "I", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "What are you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "I know I give you the same speech.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "I", "give", "you", "the", "same", "speech", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Are you concerned about that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "concerned", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Well, you know what, I just see the ads and what I read.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", "what", ",", "I", "just", "see", "the", "ads", "and", "what", "I", "read", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "Do you think it's wrong in modern day America that someone like Mitt Romney, who has made hundreds of millions of dollars and probably not quite as much as you have, Joel, but he's done OK for himself, that he gets lambasted for his success, lambasted for making that money, that somehow it's become a bad thing to be rich and successful in America?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "wrong", "in", "modern", "day", "America", "that", "someone", "like", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "who", "has", "made", "hundreds", "of", "millions", "of", "dollars", "and", "probably", "not", "quite", "as", "much", "as", "you", "have", ",", "Joel", ",", "but", "he", "'s", "done", "OK", "for", "himself", ",", "that", "he", "gets", "lambasted", "for", "his", "success", ",", "lambasted", "for", "making", "that", "money", ",", "that", "somehow", "it", "'s", "become", "a", "bad", "thing", "to", "be", "rich", "and", "successful", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["millions of dollars"], "LOCATION": ["America", "America"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Joel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "You must feel offended when you hear him say something like that, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "feel", "offended", "when", "you", "hear", "him", "say", "something", "like", "that", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Well, Piers, I'm -- Here I go again, but I'm for mercy, I'm for seeing the best in people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "'m", "--", "Here", "I", "go", "again", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "for", "mercy", ",", "I", "'m", "for", "seeing", "the", "best", "in", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Being merciful towards Mitt Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Being", "merciful", "towards", "Mitt", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "In a presidential election, every sentence is scrutinized.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "a", "presidential", "election", ",", "every", "sentence", "is", "scrutinized", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "How many have you done?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "have", "you", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "I've done four.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "done", "four", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "How many tens of millions of copies have you sold?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "tens", "of", "millions", "of", "copies", "have", "you", "sold", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "How do you convince them to take your lead?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "convince", "them", "to", "take", "your", "lead", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Well, I think the big part of the ministry is that -- you know, we faced difficulties, too, but our hearts go out to people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "big", "part", "of", "the", "ministry", "is", "that", "--", "you", "know", ",", "we", "faced", "difficulties", ",", "too", ",", "but", "our", "hearts", "go", "out", "to", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Did you worry about dipping your toe into a very hot political situation?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "worry", "about", "dipping", "your", "toe", "into", "a", "very", "hot", "political", "situation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "You know, I didn't, because, Piers, the foundation of our faith is based out of Israel.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "did", "n't", ",", "because", ",", "Piers", ",", "the", "foundation", "of", "our", "faith", "is", "based", "out", "of", "Israel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "Is he into this P-90X thing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "into", "this", "P-90X", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "Let's see.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "see", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "He works out.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "works", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Every day?", "question_tokens": ["Every", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "No, I don't work out every day.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "work", "out", "every", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "If you had Barack Obama and Mitt Romney here, you wanted them to declare things, what do you want them to declare truthfully to the electorate to make a decision about them?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "Barack", "Obama", "and", "Mitt", "Romney", "here", ",", "you", "wanted", "them", "to", "declare", "things", ",", "what", "do", "you", "want", "them", "to", "declare", "truthfully", "to", "the", "electorate", "to", "make", "a", "decision", "about", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Well, I don't know if I can give them advice.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "I", "can", "give", "them", "advice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "You think it's just poison?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "it", "'s", "just", "poison", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Well, I would love for it to, but it seems, as long as I can remember, it's always happened.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "love", "for", "it", "to", ",", "but", "it", "seems", ",", "as", "long", "as", "I", "can", "remember", ",", "it", "'s", "always", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Would you like it to stop?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "it", "to", "stop", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "I would love it to stop.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "love", "it", "to", "stop", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "What would you choose?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "I would choose -- if I was in my 20s, I would say music.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "choose", "--", "if", "I", "was", "in", "my", "20s", ",", "I", "would", "say", "music", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ray Joseph"], "LOCATION": ["Haiti", "America"]}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "What does it do to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "do", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Well, politics really came from my uncle, Ray Joseph, who was the Haiti ambassador to America.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "politics", "really", "came", "from", "my", "uncle", ",", "Ray", "Joseph", ",", "who", "was", "the", "Haiti", "ambassador", "to", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["RNC"]}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "What's that all about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "that", "all", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "The first thing is I did not agree to perform at the RNC.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "first", "thing", "is", "I", "did", "not", "agree", "to", "perform", "at", "the", "RNC", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "They are?", "question_tokens": ["They", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "Yeah, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Haiti", "Brooklyn"]}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Have you ever been a Republican, or have you always been resolutely a Democrat?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "been", "a", "Republican", ",", "or", "have", "you", "always", "been", "resolutely", "a", "Democrat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "Coming from Haiti, landing in the projects of Brooklyn, my mama was on welfare at the time.", "answer_tokens": ["Coming", "from", "Haiti", ",", "landing", "in", "the", "projects", "of", "Brooklyn", ",", "my", "mama", "was", "on", "welfare", "at", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "By the way, did you say Jean?", "question_tokens": ["By", "the", "way", ",", "did", "you", "say", "Jean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Jean.", "answer_tokens": ["Jean", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "How do you think he's done, if you're being critical?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "done", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "being", "critical", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "If I'm being critical, where we're at right now with his first term, and it -- he didn't get a bipartisan front.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "'m", "being", "critical", ",", "where", "we", "'re", "at", "right", "now", "with", "his", "first", "term", ",", "and", "it", "--", "he", "did", "n't", "get", "a", "bipartisan", "front", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "When you hear Mitt Romney, as you did yesterday in the secret tape that emerged, talking about nearly half of America being victims, living off the state, not paying taxes, a very smeary, condemning kind of rhetoric he used, what did you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "hear", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "as", "you", "did", "yesterday", "in", "the", "secret", "tape", "that", "emerged", ",", "talking", "about", "nearly", "half", "of", "America", "being", "victims", ",", "living", "off", "the", "state", ",", "not", "paying", "taxes", ",", "a", "very", "smeary", ",", "condemning", "kind", "of", "rhetoric", "he", "used", ",", "what", "did", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", ",", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "I mean, I felt offended.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "felt", "offended", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Wyclef Jean"]}, "docId": "120918pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "CD", "CD", ":", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "What do you think those who are still trying to make their minds up should really focus on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "those", "who", "are", "still", "trying", "to", "make", "their", "minds", "up", "should", "really", "focus", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "If you follow Wyclef Jean on Twitter, probably over three million -- and I probably influence a lot more than that -- I think what you should focus on is two things.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "you", "follow", "Wyclef", "Jean", "on", "Twitter", ",", "probably", "over", "three", "million", "--", "and", "I", "probably", "influence", "a", "lot", "more", "than", "that", "--", "I", "think", "what", "you", "should", "focus", "on", "is", "two", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]